<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
   <name>Processmaker</name>
   <key>processmaker</key>
   <state>stable</state>
    <logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tomolimo/processmaker/master/processmaker.png</logo>
   <description>
      <short>
		 <fr>Ce plugin fournit la possibilité d'intégrer un processus (workflow) aux tickets.</fr>
         <en>This plugin provides a process (workflow) management linked to tickets.</en>
	 <cs>Tento zásuvný modul poskytuje správu procesů (pracovní postup) napojený na požadavky.</cs>
      </short>
      <long>
         <en>This plugin is dedicated to provide a process (workflow) management linked to tickets. This goal is achieved using ProcessMaker (URL: http://www.processmaker.com/). ProcessMaker will provide Process design and Workflow execution. This plugin is the glue between GLPI and ProcessMaker.</en>
		 <fr>Ce plugin est dédié à la gestion de processus (workflows) liés à des tickets. Ce but est atteint par l'utilisation de ProcessMaker (URL: http://www.processmaker.com/). ProcessMaker fournit un outil graphique de création de processus et permet l'exécution de ceux-ci. Ce plugin sert de glue entre GLPI et ProcessMaker.</fr>
	 <cs>Tento zásuvný modul je věnován poskytnutí správy procesu (pracovní postup), napojeného na požadavky. Tohoto cíle je dosaženo použitím ProcessMaker (URL: http://www.processmaker.com/). ProcessMaker poskytne návrh procesu a vykonání pracovního postupu. Tento zásuvný modul je můstkem mezi GLPI a ProcessMaker.</cs>
      </long>
   </description>
   <homepage>https://github.com/tomolimo/processmaker</homepage>
   <download>https://github.com/tomolimo/processmaker/releases</download>
   <issues>https://github.com/tomolimo/processmaker/issues</issues>
   <readme>https://github.com/tomolimo/processmaker/wiki</readme>
   <authors>
      <author>Olivier Moron</author>
   </authors>
   <versions>
      <version>
         <num>3.3.1</num>
         <compatibility>9.2</compatibility>
      </version>
      <version>
          <num>3.3.1</num>
          <compatibility>9.1</compatibility>
      </version>
   </versions>
   <langs>
      <lang>en_gb</lang>
      <lang>fr_fr</lang>
      <lang>cs_cz</lang>
   </langs>
   <license>GPL v2+</license>
   <tags>
         <fr>
            <tag>Processus</tag>
            <tag>Workflow</tag>
			<tag>Helpdesk</tag>
			<tag>Ticket</tag>
         </fr>
         <en>
            <tag>Processes</tag>
            <tag>Helpdesk</tag>
			<tag>Workflows</tag>
			<tag>Ticket</tag>
         </en>
	 <cs>
            <tag>Procesy</tag>
            <tag>Službapodpory</tag>
	    <tag>Pracovnípostupy</tag>
	    <tag>Požadavek</tag>
         </cs>
   </tags>
</root>
